OLACK EZRA OMONDI

P.O.BOX 74260 – 00200 NAIROBI. +254 725 730 088. olackezra@yahoo.com.

Personal Profile Statement

I am a motivated, adaptable, team player and responsible Funeral Director, President, National Chairman, Accountant and Community leader who has the professional and technical skills developed through many years of work experience in the various fields. I have a methodical, customer, members, and community focused approach to work and a strong drive to see things through to completion.

Achievements

- Africa Funeral Award (AFFS) Year 2021 as the best Funeral Director
- President and founder member of Africa Federation of Funeral Services (AFFS)
- National Chairman and founder member of Funeral Services Association of Kenya(FUSAK)
- Chairman and founder member of Kaloleni Estate Residents Association (KERA)
- Introduced AFFS AND FUSAK Awards to motivate those in funeral industry
- I am the first person to conduct an Embalming seminar in Africa at Kenyatta National Hospital having brought Dominck Astorino lecturer from wayne state university and worsham college of mortuary science(USA)
- As the chairman of FUSAK I brought all mortuary attendants together and initated seminars ,workshops and Funeral conferences.
- Transformed mortuaries and funeral homes in Kenya
- As community leader and chairman national museum gazetted kaloleni social hall and all streets in kaloleni Estate as national monuments.
- Reclaimed a dumpsite into a recreational facility in Kaloleni Estate
- Implemented major computerized systems in accounting both for lee funeral home and antique auctions.

Education

1999: Kenya Accountancy Technician Course (KATC) FINAL SELF STUDY

• Final Level registration number ATC/32751

1992 – 1995: Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education KCSE GENDIA HIGH SCHOOL . Mean Grade C (PLAIN)

1991: Kenya Certificate of Primary Education KCPE NGODHE PRIMARY SCHOOL .501marks

Employment

January 2000 – Present Accountant Lee Funeral Services ltd

- Keeping up to date with latest technologies
- Managing Accounting and payroll software
- Providing extensive support to auditors on Accounting and taxation
- Computation of government taxes
- Managing vehicles register

July 2001 – Present Accountant Antique Auctions

Maintaining both clients and office accounts

Professional Body

1995 – Present National Chairman Funeral Services Association of Kenya (FUSAK)

2018 – Present President African Federation of Funeral Services (AFFS)

Qualifications

- Embalming certificate
- Funeral Home Management
- Management of the Dead

SKILLS

- Ability to handle confidential information
- Ability to prepare and present reports
- Excellent knowledge of a variety accounting software
- Excellent knowledge of the constitution
- Excellent knowledge on grief and ability to handle the bereaved families

Hobbies and Interests

I enjoy reading non – fiction books, building funeral networks, solving puzzles, researching on funeral science and socializing with friends and family

References

DR. Johansen OduorGovernment Pathologist
Ministry of Health

Mr John Lee Director and Owner Lee Funeral Services ltd